
[
  {
"question": "What is the name of our story?",
 "answers": ["The bear and the bee"],
"options": ["The angry bees", "Funny Honey","The bear and the honey"]
},

  {
  "question": "What do bears love?",
  "answers": ["Bears love honey"],
  "options": ["Bears love watermelons","Bears love cheese", "Bears love bones"]
  },

   {
  "question": "What was the bear looking for?",
  "answers": ["Looking for honey"],
  "options": ["Looking for his shoes", "Looking for his glasses","Looking for milk"]
  },

  {
  "question": "Did he find any honey?",
  "answers": ["He didn't find any honey"],
  "options": ["He found a little bit", "He found a jar full of honey","he found a can of honey"]
  },

  {
  "question": "Where did he go to find honey?",
  "answers": ["He went into the forest"],
  "options": ["He went to the market", "He went to a shop", "He went to the countryside"]
  },

  {
  "question": "What did he see in the forest?",
  "answers": ["He saw a beehive"],
  "options": ["he saw a lake", "He saw a mountain", "He saw a pumpkin"]
  },

  {
  "question": "What did he stick in the beehive?",
  "answers": ["He stuck his paw"],
  "options": [ "He stuck his nose","he stuck his tongue", "He stuck his eye"]
  },

  {
  "question": "What came out of the beehive?",
  "answers": ["A bee came out"],
  "options": [ "A squirrel came out","Nothing came out", "A cat came out"]
  },
   {
  "question": "How did the bear feel about the bee?",
  "answers": ["He felt annoyed"],
  "options": ["He felt happy", "He felt bored", "He felt great"]
  }
  ,
   {
  "question": "What did the the bear say to the bee?",
  "answers": ["I'm bigger and i am stronger than you"],
  "options": ["I like to eat your honey please", "Let's play a game", "I'm happy to see you"]
  },
  {
  "question": "What did the bear do after that?",
  "answers": ["He stuck his paw again"],
  "options": ["He apologized","He went back home", "He cried"]
  },
   {
  "question": "What was Alex's fourth idea?",
  "answers": ["Hide the medicine in a bird's nest"],
  "options": ["Hide it in an owl's nest","Hide it in the dog house", "Hide it in his bedroom"]
  },
   {
  "question": "What did the bee do?",
  "answers": ["The bee stung him"],
  "options": ["The bee flew away", "The bee cried","The bee laughed"]
  },
  {
  "question": "Where did the bee sting the bear?",
  "answers": ["It stung him on his nose"],
  "options": ["It stung him on his butt", "It stung him on his tongue", "It stung him on his bellybutton"]
  },
  {
  "question": "What did the bear do after that?",
  "answers": ["He grabbed a stick and tried to hit the bee"],
  "options": ["He cried in pain","He said 'sorry'", "He didn't do anything"]
  },
  {
  "question": "What did the bee do?",
  "answers": ["The bee flew back to the beehive"],
  "options": ["The bee cried", "The bee grabbed a stick and hit him", "The bee fell asleep"]
  },
    {
  "question": "What did the bee do?",
  "answers": ["The bee flew back to the beehive"],
  "options": ["The bee cried", "The bee grabbed a stick and hit him", "The bee fell asleep"]
  },
    {
  "question": "How many bees flew out of the beehive?",
  "answers": ["Thousands of bees"],
  "options": ["Tens of bees", "A dozen of bees", "Hundreds of bees"]
  },
   {
  "question": "What did the bees do?",
  "answers": ["Stung the bear all over his body"],
  "options": ["Screamed at the bear", "Apologized to the bear", "Gave the bear a lot of honey"]
  },
   {
  "question": "What did the bear do?",
  "answers": ["He ran back home"],
  "options": ["He fought the bees", "He played hide and seek", "He apologized"]
  },
   {
  "question": "What did the bBear give to the bear?",
  "answers": ["Bee sting medicine"],
  "options": ["A hot cup of coffee", "A honey sandwich", "A hug"]
  }
]